[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8a1"
  },
  "Question": "With inheritance, a derived subclass object can directly access any",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Easy",
  "Option1": "With inheritance, a derived subclass object can directly access any",
  "Option2": "Private superclass member",
  "Option3": "Public superclass member",
  "Option4": "Protected, public or private superclass member",
  "Correct_Answer": "Public superclass member"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8a2"
  },
  "Question": "What is the keyword used in java to create an object?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Easy",
  "Option1": "This",
  "Option2": "New",
  "Option3": "Sync",
  "Option4": "New()",
  "Correct_Answer": "New"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8a3"
  },
  "Question": "An array holds:",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Easy",
  "Option1": "Similar values of same data Type",
  "Option2": "Different values of same data Type",
  "Option3": "Same values of different data Types",
  "Option4": "Different values of different data Types",
  "Correct_Answer": "Similar values of same data Type"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8a4"
  },
  "Question": "Which of the following always need a Capital letter ?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Easy",
  "Option1": "Class names and Strings",
  "Option2": "Objects and class names",
  "Option3": "Fields and Strings",
  "Option4": "Data Types and fields",
  "Correct_Answer": "Class names and Strings"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8a5"
  },
  "Question": "The default statement of a switch is always executed.",
  "Type": "T/F",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Easy",
  "Option1": "True",
  "Option2": "False",
  "Correct_Answer": "False"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8a6"
  },
  "Question": "Following code will result in: float num = 5/0;",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Easy",
  "Option1": "Compilation error: Divisions must be in a try block",
  "Option2": "Compilation error: DivideByZeroException",
  "Option3": "Runtime Exception",
  "Option4": "No Error: a is NaN",
  "Correct_Answer": "Runtime Exception"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8a7"
  },
  "Question": "Choose the appropriate data Type for this value: \"1\" ",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Easy",
  "Option1": "String",
  "Option2": "Boolean",
  "Option3": "Int",
  "Option4": "Char",
  "Correct_Answer": "String"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8a8"
  },
  "Question": "Choose the appropriate data Type for this value: 1",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Easy",
  "Option1": "String",
  "Option2": "Int",
  "Option3": "Double",
  "Option4": "Boolean",
  "Correct_Answer": "Int"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8a9"
  },
  "Question": "Which of the following is not a Java keyword?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Easy",
  "Option1": "Main",
  "Option2": "Try",
  "Option3": "Integer",
  "Option4": "String",
  "Correct_Answer": "Integer"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8aa"
  },
  "Question": "Can you compare a boolean to an integer?",
  "Type": "T/F",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Easy",
  "Option1": "True",
  "Option2": "False",
  "Correct_Answer": "False"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8ab"
  },
  "Question": "What is the size of a Char in Java?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Easy",
  "Option1": "4 bits",
  "Option2": "7 bits",
  "Option3": "8 bits",
  "Option4": "16 bits",
  "Correct_Answer": "16 bits"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8ac"
  },
  "Question": "Primitive data Types are allocated on a stack",
  "Type": "T/F",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Easy",
  "Option1": "True",
  "Option2": "False",
  "Correct_Answer": "True"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8ad"
  },
  "Question": "Choose the appropriate data Type for this field: kindOfBird",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Easy",
  "Option1": "String",
  "Option2": "Int",
  "Option3": "Boolean",
  "Option4": "Double",
  "Correct_Answer": "String"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8ae"
  },
  "Question": "Following code will result in: int num = 6.7;",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Easy",
  "Option1": "Compilation error",
  "Option2": "Runtime error",
  "Option3": "Num being 6.7",
  "Option4": "Num being 6",
  "Correct_Answer": "Compilation error"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8af"
  },
  "Question": "A null reference may be used to access a static variable or method.",
  "Type": "T/F",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "True",
  "Option2": "False",
  "Correct_Answer": "False"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8b0"
  },
  "Question": "If none of the private/protected/public is specified for a member, that member..",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "Is accessible publicly",
  "Option2": "Is only accessible by other classes of the same package",
  "Option3": "Is only accessible from within the class",
  "Option4": "Is accessible by the class and its subclasses",
  "Correct_Answer": "Is only accessible by other classes of the same package"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8b1"
  },
  "Question": "Given the declaration : int [ ] ar = {1,2,3,4,5}; What is the value of ar[4]?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "2",
  "Option2": "3",
  "Option3": "4",
  "Option4": "5",
  "Correct_Answer": "5"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8b2"
  },
  "Question": "Which one needs a web page to run",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "Which one needs a web page to run",
  "Option2": "A Java Stand-Alone Application",
  "Option3": "A Java Applet",
  "Option4": "A Java Class",
  "Correct_Answer": "A Java Applet"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8b3"
  },
  "Question": "Which is not a part of defining an object?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "Description",
  "Option2": "Methods",
  "Option3": "Associations with other objects",
  "Option4": "Name",
  "Correct_Answer": "Description"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8b4"
  },
  "Question": "The methods wait(), notify() and notifyAll() in Object need to be called from synchronized pieces of code.",
  "Type": "T/F",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "True",
  "Option2": "False",
  "Correct_Answer": "True"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8b5"
  },
  "Question": "An object could be ...",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "Anything",
  "Option2": "A data container",
  "Option3": "A program",
  "Option4": "An Algorithm",
  "Correct_Answer": "Anything"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8b6"
  },
  "Question": "Inner classes can be defined within methods.",
  "Type": "T/F",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "True",
  "Option2": "False",
  "Correct_Answer": "True"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8b7"
  },
  "Question": "What is the main function of any variable?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "To add numbers together",
  "Option2": "To keep track of data in the memory of the computer",
  "Option3": "To print words on the screen",
  "Option4": "To write Java codes",
  "Correct_Answer": "To keep track of data in the memory of the computer"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8b8"
  },
  "Question": "Methods that are marked protected can be called in any subclass of that class.",
  "Type": "T/F",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "True",
  "Option2": "False",
  "Correct_Answer": "True"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8b9"
  },
  "Question": "The last value in an array called ar can be found at index:",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "0",
  "Option2": "1",
  "Option3": "Ar.length",
  "Option4": "Ar.length - 1",
  "Correct_Answer": "Ar.length - 1"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8ba"
  },
  "Question": "Choose the best definition of an object",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "A Thing",
  "Option2": "An instance of a class",
  "Option3": "Something you wear",
  "Option4": "Variable",
  "Correct_Answer": "An instance of a class"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8bb"
  },
  "Question": "An abstract class can have non-abstract methods.",
  "Type": "T/F",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "True",
  "Option2": "False",
  "Correct_Answer": "True"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8bc"
  },
  "Question": "What is the difference between private and public functions?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "Public functions are free, you have to buy private ones",
  "Option2": "Public functions are the only ones you can download",
  "Option3": "Public functions can be used by anyone, private can only be used by other code in the class you are writing",
  "Option4": "Public functions canâ€™t be used",
  "Correct_Answer": "Public functions can be used by anyone, private can only be used by other code in the class you are writing"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8bd"
  },
  "Question": "What is an instanceof?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Medium",
  "Option1": "A methods in object",
  "Option2": "An operator and keyword",
  "Option3": "An operator only",
  "Option4": "A keyword only",
  "Correct_Answer": "An operator and keyword"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8be"
  },
  "Question": "Native methods can be \"abstract\"",
  "Type": "T/F",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "True",
  "Option2": "False",
  "Correct_Answer": "False"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8bf"
  },
  "Question": "Which one could be used as the main container in a Java application?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "JApplet",
  "Option2": "JFrame",
  "Option3": "JPanel",
  "Option4": "JButton",
  "Correct_Answer": "JFrame"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8c0"
  },
  "Question": "How to define a JButton with the caption test?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "JButton aButton(\"test\");",
  "Option2": "JButton aButton=new JButton(\"test\");",
  "Option3": "JButton aButton=new JButton(test);",
  "Option4": "Button(\"test\") aButton;",
  "Correct_Answer": "JButton aButton=new JButton(\"test\");"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8c1"
  },
  "Question": "A UML association from class A to class B means",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "Class B inherits from Class A",
  "Option2": "Class B is defined within class A",
  "Option3": "Class B has an attribute of Type A",
  "Option4": "Class A has an attribute of Type B",
  "Correct_Answer": "Class A has an attribute of Type B"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8c2"
  },
  "Question": "Class B inherits from Class A, what cannot be said:",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "B is a sub-class of A",
  "Option2": "A is a super-class of B",
  "Option3": "B has access to private members of A",
  "Option4": "B has access to protected members of A",
  "Correct_Answer": "B has access to private members of A"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8c3"
  },
  "Question": "A class can be transient.",
  "Type": "T/F",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "True",
  "Option2": "False",
  "Correct_Answer": "False"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8c4"
  },
  "Question": "What is an Applet?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "AA Java program that does not run through a web browser",
  "Option2": "A Java program that is run through a web browser",
  "Option3": "An object-oriented programming language",
  "Option4": "An interactive website",
  "Correct_Answer": "A Java program that is run through a web browser"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8c5"
  },
  "Question": "Java keywords are written in lowercase as well as uppercase.",
  "Type": "T/F",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "True",
  "Option2": "False",
  "Correct_Answer": "False"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8c6"
  },
  "Question": "What does AWT stands for?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "Advanced Window Toolkit",
  "Option2": "Abstract window Toolkit",
  "Option3": "Adjust Window Toolkit",
  "Option4": "None of the choices",
  "Correct_Answer": "Abstract window Toolkit"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8c7"
  },
  "Question": "In an instance method or a constructor, \"this\" is a reference to the current object.",
  "Type": "T/F",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "True",
  "Option2": "False",
  "Correct_Answer": "True"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8c8"
  },
  "Question": " _____ is used to find and fix bugs in the Java programs.",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "JVM",
  "Option2": "JRE",
  "Option3": "JDK",
  "Option4": "JDB",
  "Correct_Answer": "JDB"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8c9"
  },
  "Question": "What is the return Type of the hashCode() method in the Object class?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "Object",
  "Option2": "Int",
  "Option3": "Long",
  "Option4": "Void",
  "Correct_Answer": "Int"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8ca"
  },
  "Question": "Garbage Collection is manual process.",
  "Type": "T/F",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "True",
  "Option2": "False",
  "Correct_Answer": "False"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8cb"
  },
  "Question": " What do you mean by nameless objects?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "An object created by using the new keyword.",
  "Option2": "An object of a superclass created in the subclass.",
  "Option3": "An object without having any name but having a reference.",
  "Option4": "An object that has no reference.",
  "Correct_Answer": "An object that has no reference."
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61990f585236ee483c8ea8cc"
  },
  "Question": "Which of the following is an immediate subclass of the Panel class?",
  "Type": "MCQ",
  "Difficulty_Level": "Hard",
  "Option1": "Applet class",
  "Option2": "Window class",
  "Option3": "Frame class",
  "Option4": "Dialog class",
  "Correct_Answer": "Applet class"
}]